Ildebrando Quinchoa

Experienced FrontEnd Developer with ability to adapt to in both self-starting and collaborative environments. On the BackEnd side I've got experience with Django building websites and REST APIs, PHP, the CMV pattern and Database Design. Open to any position where my skills are best fit.

Experience

Lead Buyer Hub LLC

Remote

October 2022 – Current

Frontend Developer

- Converted website mockups into fully responsive, cross-browser compatible and high-performance websites
- Utilized Filezilla and FTP to have access to the server and upload completed work.
- Created PHP server and MySQL database to receive and save data from a Twilio webhook.

Azordev Frontend Developer Remote December 2021 – June 2022

- Played a key role in the design and development of interactive websites
- Used React.js, Redux, Styled-Components
- Consumed APIs, using JWT tokens for authentication.
- Translated mockups and wireframes into responsive layouts and reusable components.

Projects

Django Notes App

Web Developer

June, 2022 - July, 2022

- Developed the backend of the app, using Django and Sqlite.
- Implemented local and external authentication, using OAuth with Google API.
- Designed a fully responsive Frontend for the app.
- Provided printing and pdf saving options for notes.

Chat App

https://chatapp-kappa-coral.vercel.app/

February, 2023

- Developed multi-user chat functionality using WebSockets.
- Constructed server using Node.js
- Implemented fully responsive frontend, using React.js

Education

UNEGComputer Science

Guayana, Venezuela

(2018-)

Volunteer Experience

ESBARATAO Web developer

Remote

July 2022 - Current

• Assisted in the development of a website for a non-profit organization

Skills & Interests

Technical: React.js, Javascript, PHP, Django, Python, CSS, SQL, MySQL, Sqlite, Sass, BEM, Javascript,

HTML, GIT, jQuery, RESTFUL API, Redux, Tests.

Language: Spanish, native. English, C2, Portugues, B2.